All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, thousands of feet below sea level, they set sail to the next step of their journey, Fishman Island.
Only by passing through its waters may they reach the New World.
There! Perfect!
That contraption is called the Flutter Kick Coating!
It's an extravehicular diving suit!
Wait a sec! You guys forgot the safety ropes!
Rocket launcher!
Not another one!
Eh? Guard point!
Everyone okay?
Now, build slow!
Gigantesco mano!
No!
Everybody did great!
Now, guess it's my turn.
Lost in the deep sea, the Straw Hats get separated!
Now, third gear!
Armament Tartnik!
What the hell is that?
It must be a new move!
So tough!
Underwater!
Come on!
Crap, it doesn't look like that octopus is gonna wait patiently.
Blue Walk!
Oh my! Sanji just left his bubble!
He's fast even in the sea!
Like a fish man!
So cool!
I spent two years running from those monsters on that island.
And the first thing I do is run straight at another one.
But all things considered, this one's a bit cuter, really.
Diable Jambe!
And Queen!
We'll shoot!
Can't hold my breath much longer!
overall...
Ah-ah-ah!
Can't hold my breath much longer!
Three-sword style, crossing the Six Paths.
I thought this thing was supposed to be some kind of legend. Pathetic.
All I've done is fight these last few years.
It sounds awful when I think about it, but I'm actually grateful for it.
But I still haven't surpassed him yet.
And that's why I'll keep getting stronger.
Wow!
I couldn't even see his attack!
I could have handled that on my own.
You say something, Number Seven?
I will kill you dead.
You can try.
Why are you two not listening to me?
I told you not to cut it!
My turn!
GUMGUM!
Elephant God!
He blew it away!
What kind of training did Luffy go through?
He did it underwater, no less!
What the?
You guys see that?
It's a shark!
Huh.
Yeah, why is that shark wearing a shirt?
Not to mention it's huge.
What's it doing?
Thanking us for helping it, maybe?
Nice manners for a fish, huh?
What's up?
The sea current is pulling us in.
That's not good.
Let's get back to the sunny.
Yeah!
the sea.
They're being swept away by the downward current!
You can't get split up down here!
Follow them!
Right!
I don't want to die down here!
It's dark and wet!
What, you fools?
Pulling together!
Eh?
Huh?
If I had a stomach, I would be fighting its conscience right now!
Keep it your quibble, Frankie! Turn hard to port, otherwise we're gonna crash!
Alright, I'm on it!
Don't let up for a second or the shove's a corner!
Let's keep it together, everybody!
Stay in the center of the current!
I'm doing my best!
It's way too fast!
This is awesome!
You're awake!
What a headache!
But at least we made it!
Hm?
What's wrong? Why are you all making such long faces?
I mean, I'm awake now, so there's nothing for you to fear!
Man, is it freezing!
Luffy, Zoro, and Sanji have gone missing!
They're lost in the sea!
What?!
The most we can do now is hope the monster didn't tear them apart!
Glad you're being optimistic!
How are we supposed to find them when we can't even see what's in front of us?
I don't like being in the dark!
It feels like something could attack us from any direction!
The best I can guess is we've descended about 7,000 meters!
Even the sharks submerged can't sustain this level of pressure!
How close are we to Fishman Island?
Maybe the only way we can't find them!
How are we supposed to find them when we can't even see what's in front of us?
I don't like being in the dark!
It feels like something could attack us from any direction!
The best I can guess is we've descended about 7,000 meters!
Even the sharks submerged can't sustain this level of pressure!
How close are we to Fishman Island?
Maybe the others have already made it there!
Probably not.
According to Kami, it's 10,000 meters below sea level!
We have 3,000 more to go?!
Those guys each have a bubble and that's all!
Even if they are somehow still alive,
they'll need more air!
None of this would have happened if they used the safety ropes!
Freaking out's not helping!
So let's get to work!
We can look for them with my new searchlight!
Whoa!
Does it shine from your eyes?!
Hmm, you'll see!
Frankie Nipple Lights!
Why do they have to be there?!
Oh wow!
So huge!
Scary!
No!
There's no way!
Let's get out of here!
Alright everybody, keep your eyes peeled!
They gotta be looking for us!
With any luck, we'll find each other!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Where in the world have you guys gone?!
We need you all back!
Come out, come out wherever you are!
Any time now!
Really!
Damn it all!
This place is so fast and we're so far down!
Sunny's eyes are practically useless!
I feel so helpless!
We can barely see!
It's no wonder that everyone is on edge!
There's gotta be a better way to tackle this!
You ladies got any ideas?
Keep searching and just hope for the best!
We can't stop the ship right now!
Surely they haven't gone too far yet!
We can't give up on them!
Right!
Look!
A jellyfish!
It's like we're inside it!
It's huge!
It feels like it could swallow us whole!
And they're twinkling!
It's like a starry sky wherever they go!
They're so beautiful!
Whoa!
That's one long tentacle!
You, uh, wanna shake hands and be friends?
Whatever you do, don't touch it!
It's probably venomous!
Ahh!
Oh crap!
No choice!
Coup de Burst!
No way!
It ain't that big jellyfish hole!
Oh, look!
You're so beautiful!
Can't pick each other up?
Oh!
Whoa!
Oh, my gosh!
You're so beautiful!
Oh, that's one long tentacle!
You, uh, wanna shake hands and be friends?
Whatever you do, don't touch it!
Huh?
It's probably venomous!
Ahhh!
Ah!
Crap!
No choice!
Coup de Burst!
Jellyfish holes!
Uh, not to mention, we lost some air in that maneuver.
It was better than the alternative.
Huh?
But yeah, the coup de burst sucks in air
to make a quick launch.
Thing is, because we're underwater,
it's only resources our air supply.
So obviously, when we use it, our bubble shrinks a bit.
That makes sense.
But it doesn't make me feel better
about our coating deflating.
The fish that attacked it turned upside down!
A neurotoxin, I figured as much.
It's awful down here, and dark.
It's scary, all these creepy creatures
with their freaky eyes.
Because the sea's so dark,
many of the animals that live down here have poor eyesight.
So they can't see any better than us?
Hey, losers, where you looking?
However, there are some
that have very developed eyes as well.
hopeful
Oh, you're curious
as to how I can see when I don't have eyes?
Of course you are.
But do you really want to know the answer?
Drum roll.
It's a secret.
Hey, Brooke, why is it you're always talking to yourself?
It's a habit that comes from being lonely.
Enough!
Quit fooling around!
No more violence, please!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Help us!
Nami is scary!
What's this?
Well, that's not good.
Hey, guys?
Huh?
Have any of you seen the pirate who boarded the ship?
Oh, yeah, I forgot about him.
I'm sure he's around here somewhere.
But where is somewhere?
I haven't seen him for a while.
Not since we descended.
Do you think he might have been thrown off when everything went crazy?
Totally possible.
I mean, his arms and legs were tied up.
There's no way he could hold on to anything while we were rocking around.
Normally I'd agree.
But it seems that he freed himself.
Look.
So that drippy weirdo escaped and he's... still here?
He's gotta be waiting us out for a moment to attack.
This is bad.
If you're so eager to see me, I'd be happy to sneak into your room tonight, sweetheart.
Hmm...
Damn it!
We've got enough problems.
We don't need this guy giving us one more thing to worry about!
Don't get worked up.
It's not like he's an actual threat to any of us.
Hehehehe.
That's right.
You think that.
You'll see how wrong you are now that the three morons who could put up a fight have gotten themselves killed fighting that kraken.
Hehehehe.
After all, there's no way they survived getting sucked down into the bowels of the ocean with just those tiny bubbles to protect them.
Huh?
What a shame I didn't have the chance to kill Straw Hat with my own hands.
But no one will ever doubt that he's dead once I come back with the rest of his crew members' heads in tow as my personal trophies.
No one at all.
Hehehehe.
But I can't get too excited.
There's no need to rush.
If I killed them all now, there wouldn't be anyone left to sail the ship.
And then what would I do?
So I'll let them live for now while they can still be useful to me.
Once we land on Fishman Island, though, I'm gonna slaughter you down to the last man.
Hehehehe.
I found him, guys!
Hey!
Not knocking off, dammit!
I wasn't doing anything bad!
I swear!
Let's see him break out of that.
I found him, guys!
Hey! Not knocking off, dammit!
I wasn't doing anything bad, I swear!
Let's see him break out of that.
How did he even manage to get in there?
Because we weren't paying attention to him.
If he weren't so stupid, we could have been in trouble.
His body was like a big mass of goo in there.
It didn't have a real shape.
So he was like a pile of mud?
Yeah, if I had to guess, it's a devil fruit power.
Most likely a Logia-type fruit at that.
He was giving us a false sense of security,
because he could have escaped at any time.
Get me out of here! I'll behave, I swear!
You and the banana hammock!
If you let me out, I'll be your servant!
Come on!
You feeling all right, Chopper?
I don't know.
It just got really hot.
I can't stand the heat.
I'm dying.
Sheesh!
It is warmer.
Wait a second.
Is that smoke?
We can't see what's in front of us through that!
Smoke under the wire?
Can't be.
Actually, it can.
Is that...
Hydrothermal deposits!
What?
Keep up!
This is a volcanic area!
For real?
Yes, for real!
You can see where there have been eruptions!
We have to get out of here now!
If one of those erupts, we're as good as dead!
It's hot.
I'm so hot.
Ugh.
There's something coming after us!
It's carnivorous tube worms!
Got no choice.
Small one.
Coup de burst!
No!
Traceless crabs!
Have to risk it again!
Coup de burst!
Ah!
I don't even know what the hell those things are!
Hang on, guys!
Coup de burst!
The sea is awful!
I hate it!
There's no way the others can survive down here on their own!
I can't believe this is happening!
And we'd only just gotten back together!
Stop crying!
Those three are way too tough to die!
Even using Coup de burst that sparingly, we've lost so much air already!
What is that?
A light?
In the darkness?
Wait!
Is that Fishman Island?
Maybe Luffy beat us there!
It can't be!
We haven't descended the last 3,000 meters!
Who are you?
A friend?
Stop!
If you want to flash signals, do it without actually flashing!
Can you tell what it is?
No, it's still too bright to see!
Oh no!
An anglerfish!
We're screwed!
The deep sea hunter fooled us hook, line, and sinker!
A little close that time!
There isn't anywhere left for us to run!
What can we do?
This can't be happening!
It's human?
No, this doesn't make any sense!
A sea monster?
That's taking the form of a man!
It's a sea monster!
He's going to cat-size the ship!
What the?
Hey, that's naughty!
You know better, Ancaro!
You're not allowed to eat ships!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Captain Vander Decken won't be happy when he hears about this!
Wait, did he just help us?
Who freaking cares?
Let's just make a break for it!
He might change his mind!
Ohhhh!
Aaaaaahhhhhh!
O-o-o-o-o-o-o!
Gah!
Please no more!
O-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o!
The legendary ghost ship the Flying Dutchman emerges from the darkness, closing in on the horrified Straw Hats.
However, before they encounter its creepy captain, a volcano erupts, sending them diving into a trench.
What they find there is not the seafloor, but another deadly nightmare.
On the next One Piece, undersea volcanic eruption, drifting to the Fishman Island, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!